准备好了没  老爸
Almost ready, dad?
我们得赶紧开始训练了
We got to get a little practice in.
我在系鞋带
Just lacing up.
老爸  故意拖延比赛
Delay of game on dad!
听着  帕克  如果你要做我们的裁判
Okay, Parker, if you want to be our ref,
你至少要等到比赛开始吧
at least wait until we start playing.
顶撞裁判
Talking back to the ref,
技术犯规
technical foul!
你这穿的是什么东西
What are those?
超短裤
Those are shorts.
这种裤子代表了服饰史上的一段黑暗时期
It was a dark time in fashion before you were born.
这是皮特·鲁尼在职业巅峰时候的好运裤
These are prime-time Pete Rooney's lucky shorts.
当年的州冠军  现在重返江湖
to the state championship, so he's wearing them now.
当皮特·鲁尼直呼自己的名字
And when he talks about himself in the third person,
他就已经准备好重振雄风
it means prime-time Pete Rooney's fixing to win.
最近城里有一场老少配
Our town has a big two-on-two tournament
二对二篮球联赛
where an adult teams up with a kid
呵呵  这比赛从来就没有女孩赢过
and, uh, ha, no girl's ever won...
直到现在
Till now.
我的意思是我会是第一位在这场比赛摘得桂冠的女孩
I was saying that I'm gonna be the first girl to win.
是不是我不说  哈  怎样  就不清楚来着  哦  好吧
Was that not clear without the "bam, what?" Yeah, okay.
哈  怎样
Bam! What?!
好吧  老爸
Okay, dad.
我见过你在球场边运筹帷幄指点江山
I've seen you holding a clipboard on the court.
现在看看你还能不能打球
Now let's see if you can still play.
哦  我的球技可没退化
Oh, I can still play.
看好了  怎样
Check it. What?
球技还是有点退化了
Just a little rusty.
走步
Traveling!
- 走步  - 对的
- Traveling? - Yeah.
你的超短裤走得你的屁股都晒太阳了
Those tiny shorts are traveling right up your butt.
最好的朋友
Better in stereo
不同的朋友
b... b... better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
- I'm up with the sunshine - let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
- I lace up my high tops - oh no
扣篮  热热身
- slam dunk - ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
- I'm under the spotlight - holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
I'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go, go, go
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the other half of me, me
学不来的朋友
the half I'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the better half of me, me
离不开的朋友
the half I'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.
呼
Whew.
这绝不简单
This is tough.
我却偏偏运动天赋不佳
but I am not particularly gifted in the sports department.
就你这样子  一看就知道你几斤几两了
Trust me. It looks like it.
（此人由 NBA 火箭队中锋德怀特·霍华德扮演）
我有把这个球
Oh, I am dying
从你身下踢走的欲望
to kick that ball out from under you.
不过看来你给
But you seem
自己找了个保镖嘛
to have gotten yourself a bodyguard.
帕克  这是伯纳德
Parker, this is Bernard.
商场抽奖  房车一辆
I entered a raffle at the mall to win a personal trailer.
没想到一字之差  成了运动教练
Turns out it was for a personal trainer...
而我偏偏不需要这个
Which I do not need.
乔伊  你这缺乏运动都明摆着了  还整房车继续拒绝运动
Joey, you need a trainer much more than you need a trailer.
大个子兄弟  我不这么认为
I respectfully disagree, tree top.
房车就像是装了轮子的洗手间
A trailer's like a bathroom on wheels.
只有想不到没有做不到啊
The possibilities are endless.
私人教练可以为你在健身和营养方面指点迷津
A trainer can give you tips on fitness and nutrition,
还能让你的生活更快乐
but also make your lives happier...
更健康
And healthier.
我已经很快乐了
I'm already happy
而且也比较健康
and healthy-ish.
乔伊  在你这么大的时候
Joey, when I was your age,
我也不喜欢运动
I hated to work out too.
女孩们肆意嘲笑伯纳德 1.0
The ladies laughed at Bernard 1.0.
不过现在女士们可就喜欢伯纳德 2.0 得多
But the ladies love Bernard 2.0 much more.
我想要妹子们喜欢我
Oh, I want the ladies to love me...
至少知道我的存在
Or at least know that I'm alive.
我就是一块
I am a pathetic
空白的材料
lump of Clay.
您开始吧
Mold me.
嘿  丽芙
Oh, hey, Liv.
哦  你坐在这里看书啊
Oh, sitting and reading.
我还记得当年我有空就坐下来看书呢
I remember when I used to have time for that.
对哦  这是戏剧社要排演的节目
Yeah, it's a play that the drama club is doing.
他们请我演主角
And they offered me the lead.
不错
Fun.
你在《放声高歌》之后的舞台首秀
Your first role since sing it loud.
嗯  请你别再这样了
Yeah, please don't ever do that again.
这个节目是关于一个母亲
It's a story about a working mother
试图平衡她的事业  家庭和孩子
who struggles to juggle her career, home, and kids.
我真不知道我能不能胜任
I'm just really not sure that I can pull it off.
我天天都这么想
I have that same thought every day of my life.
不过  这个角色是不是真的有必要
But, like, do we really want to play a character who is
这么辛劳  以至于
so overworked and haggard
只能勉强苟且度日
that she can barely make it through her day?
- 这听上去很辛苦啊  - 是啊
- Wow, that does sound terrible. - Yeah.
剧情里面是不是还有一个
Well, is there another character in the play
单身无后的角色
who's single and doesn't have kids?
- 就她姐姐  - 你就演她吧
- Actually, her sister. - Play her.
嘿  玛蒂
Hey, madds.
你和老爸排练的怎样
Rehearsal any better with dad today?
首先  这叫训练
Okay, one, it's called practice.
然后  排练整个就一团糟
Two, rehearsal was a disaster.
他跑不动  投篮投不进
He's running slower. He's shooting worse.
然后他的短裤比以往更短了
And somehow his shorts got even shorter.
这是不是意味着你成不了
Does this mean that you aren't gonna be
赢得选美  比赛的第一个女孩
the first girl to win the pageant... tournament?
这话才出口我就知道我错了
I knew it was wrong the second I said it.
跟老爸组队的话我肯定赢不了
Well, I'm certainly not gonna win with dad on my team.
那我怎么办
What do I do?
这样吧  我以前曾经
Okay. Here is an exercise
这么解决这种问题
that I've done in the past.
闭上眼睛  开始全神贯注
Close your eyes and let's visualize
冥想这个问题的最佳解决方案
the best possible solution to your problem.
丽芙  玛蒂
Liv, Maddie,
这位是伯纳德  我的私人教练
this is Bernard, my personal trainer.
他会帮我变“厉害”
He's gonna get me all jacked!
（jacked：受药物影响的）
他说是把我练成肌肉男
Which he says means muscular.
幸会幸会
Nice to meet you.
你家的垃圾筒在哪里
Um, where is the trash?
谢谢夸奖  我当年大学里打过一段时间的篮球
Thank you. I played a little college ball back in the day.
嘿  乔伊  健身房在那里
But come on, Joey. The gym is that way.
我得把你练得更“壮”
I got to get you ripped.
（ripped：受药物影响的）
“壮”那也是让我变的肌肉发达
"Ripped," that also means muscular.
呵呵  冥想从来没有
Okay, the visualization thing
这么有效过
has never  worked that well before.
看来这是要让我把老爸踢走的架势
So that was the universe telling me to dump dad, right?
这不摆明了你应该把老爸踹了么
The universe is screaming at you to dump dad.
既然都这样了
Let's ride this wave.
好吧  我们再闭上眼睛
Okay, now close your eyes with me
一起冥想莱恩·戈斯林
and let's visualize Ryan gosling.
- 你好啊  队友  - 你好啊  教练
- Hey, teammate. - Hey, coach.
关于这次联赛  我想和你谈谈
I need to talk to you about the tournament.
不错  我正好也在练习步法
Great. I've been working on my jumper,
把比赛的节奏找回来了
getting my rhythm back.
什么  哦
What? Oh.
嗯  老爸  嗯
Yeah, so, dad, um...
我们两个打球真的不错
You and I have had some really great times together.
不过我不觉得我们能有什么结果
I just don't think that it's gonna work out.
你的意思是
What are you saying?
我得跟你掰了
I'm breaking up with you.
啥
What?
为什么  我做了什么了  我能改的
Why? What did I do? I can change.
我能变得更好的啊
I can be better.
听着  问题不在于你  而在于我
See, it's not you, it's me.
我是你爸
But I'm your dad.
放心  在我心中你始终会有
Right, and I will always have a...
特别的一块地方的
Special place in my heart for you,
不过现在是时候我该找别人了
but it's just time that I move on.
我认为长远看来  这样对我们两个都有好处
I think in the long run, this is gonna be better for both of us.
哇  哇  意想不到
Wow. Wow. I can't believe this.
我觉得我们两个应该在一起的的
I thought we were good together, you and me.
尴尬哟
This is awkward.
老爸  我希望和别人一起
Dad, there's someone else.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我没事  你懂的
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm fine, you know.
只是有点吃惊  不过我没事
Just a little surprised, but it's cool, you know.
你转向左  我面向右
You do you. I'll do me.
我回家还是跟老妈走吧
Maybe I'll just get a ride home with mom.
我觉得这样对我们两个都好
I think that would be best.
多谢你愿意
Thank you so much
加入我的队伍  伯纳德
for agreeing to be on my team, Bernard.
当然了  队友  我很乐意
Sure thing, teammate. I'm so excited.
来吧  击掌
Now, hit me up top.
能不能下来点
How about I hit you up the middle?
好的
Okay.
我们两个要加紧训练  准备拿下那场联赛  哈  怎样
Now, let's win this tournament. Bam! What?!
不错啊  我能试试么
I like that. Can I give it a try?
你懂得  这是我的菜
I mean, you know, it's kind of my thing,
试试看吧
but try it.
好吧
Okay.
哈  怎样
Bam! What?!
兄弟  你说“哈  怎样”和我一样自然啊
You, my good sir, are a natural bam-what-er.
来吧  开始吧
Let's do this, come on.
好吧
Okay.
你得稍微
Just got to get a little...
你得稍微热热身  对吧  伯纳德
Just got to get a little warmed up, right, Bernie?
嗯  你这
I... I think you... uh...
你应该单手拍球
It's more of like a... Like... like one hand.
赞
Yes!
我打在背板上了
I hit the backboard.
我很给力哦
I am on fire.
呃  伯纳德
Uh, Bernard?
你说你大学里面打过篮球
Thought you said you played in college.
全国垃圾桶篮球联赛
In the national trash can basketball association.
坐在在办公室椅子上
We used to roll around on office chairs
往垃圾桶里面扔纸团
and shoot up wadded-up paper. Whoo.
呃  垃圾桶篮球
Uh, trash can basketball?
- 对的  垃圾桶篮球  - 哦
- Yeah, trash can basketball. - Oh.
我连续三年都是
I won defensive player of the year
最佳后卫
three years in a row.
哦  好吧
Yes, okay?
我以貌取人了
I judged a book by its cover.
不过拜托
But come on!
这人丈二高啊
It was a seven-foot book!
嘿  妈
Hey, mom.
你在这真好
I'm so glad you're here.
关于这个角色  我考虑了很久
So I've been thinking about this role
我觉得我的理解方向错了
and I think I had it all wrong.
她不是个过度操劳的家庭主妇
She's not a haggard, broken-down housewife.
而是个超级老妈
She's a super-mom
无往不利  风度翩翩
who gets it all done and looks great doing it.
为了准备演好那个角色
So to prepare for that role,
我想我知道体验生活的最佳人选了
I think I know the perfect person to talk to.
这  你真好
That is... that is so sweet.
我的德语老师  莱夫施奈德女士
Mrs. Reifschneider, my German teacher.
有住家保姆的那位
The one with the live-in housekeeper?
很好  不错  去吧
Yeah. Yeah! Yeah!
去体验她的生活吧  去吧
Ask her. Ask her.
丽芙  我有大麻烦了
Liv, I have a huge problem.
洗耳恭听
Uh, I'm listening.
我的麻烦是伯纳德
Okay, it's just the thing with Bernard is...
等等  等等
Uh, hold on. Hold on.
妈
Mom!
啥
Huh?
您介意不
Do you mind?
何止一点点
More than you know.
- 继续  - 好的  只是
- Go on. - Okay, I just...
我本来觉得伯纳德会是个不错的队友
I thought Bernard would be a better teammate,
结果没想到他的球技糟糕透顶
but he's terrible.
比老爸还臭
Worse than dad?
臭不可闻
Way worse than dad.
他的裤子呢
Are his shorts as bad?
裤子倒没有比老爸的更难看的
No shorts are that bad.
关键在于我要是和伯纳德组队
But the point is I'm not gonna
我怎么找都赢不了那场联赛
win the tournament with Bernard.
我得想个办法把他踢掉
So I need to figure out a way to ditch him
回头找老爸
and get dad back.
你怎么突然要回到老爸身边了
Why would you want dad back?
到这个节骨眼上再想换队友已经不现实了
Because it's too late to get anyone else...
何况他是我爸  我深爱着他
And because he's my father and I love him.
我怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我觉得你知道了
Oh, I think you know.
闭上眼睛  一起冥想
Close your eyes and let's visualize
这个问题最好的解决方案
the best possible solution to your problem.
看啊  我是个水果维京海盗
Check it out. I'm a fruit viking.
好了  伯纳德
All right, Bernard.
我根据合理的预期值
Now, I have set a fitness goal for myself
给自己设定了一个健身目标
based on completely reasonable expectations.
我想要你
I want you to make me
把我训练成乔伊 2.5
into Joey 2.5.
不错吧  呵呵
Uh, ah? Nice, huh?
我的肩膀比你的还宽呢
I even have shoulders bigger than yours.
天底下没有一个人的肩膀比我的宽
Nobody has shoulders bigger than me.
比这个肩膀宽的
The only shoulder in the world bigger than this one
只有这边的
is this one.
抱歉了  兄弟  但这就是事实
Sorry, but it's true.
你今天打算怎么训练
Okay, so what's the plan for today?
乔伊  我先要确定一下
All right, Joey, I want to determine
你的基准心率
your target heart rate.
我们做几个下蹲起立
We're gonna do some squats,
做几个仰卧起坐
some crunches,
然后再慢跑几英里
Then we're gonna jog a couple Miles.
那是什么声音
What is that noise?
没想到你就光听我谈论运动
Somehow, you've exceeded your target heart rate
心率就飚的这么高
by just listening to me talk about exercise.
那么就是说我们今天的目标达成了咯
So, we're done for the day.
乔伊  我们还没开始呢
Joey, we haven't even started yet.
准备流汗吧
Now, get ready to sweat!
这真好玩
This is fun.
对心血管又好
Plus, it's great cardio
而且关节压力不大
and it's easy on the joints.
压力不大
Oh, easy,
正如我意
that is the word I've been looking for.
这下你能锻炼四肢
You can totally blast your quads
很均衡的全身运动
and get a great core workout
你只要来回跳跃
by just hopping from side-to-side.
算了  兄弟
Nah, man.
我原地跳跳就行了
I'm good just boinging in place.
乔伊 2.5 不是靠原地跳出来的
Joey 2.5 doesn't boing in place!
不要啊  够了
No! Hey! We're done.
够了  你的意思我懂了
We're done. You've made your point.
- 够了  - 我能加入么
- We're done. - May I?
来吧
Please do.
不要啊  来人啊
No! Somebody!
行了
Okay, we're done.
爸  我们能谈谈么
Hey, dad. Can we talk?
说吧
Sure.
好像我们上次谈的很有成果似的
Since it went so well the last time we did.
爸  我犯了个错误
Look, I made a mistake.
我觉得我终于理解我们一起打球的目的
I think I finally realized that the whole point
是为了一起赢下那场联赛
was for us to win this tournament together.
是啊  那是我们打球的目的
You're right. That was the whole point.
既然这样  那就继续训练吧
Well, back to practice.
真的  我这就去换衣服
Really? I'm gonna go get changed.
哦  不  不  不
Oh, no, no, no.
我不是和你训练
Not with you...
我找了个新队友
With my new teammate.
你找了个什么
Your new what-mate?
迪吉
Diggy?
别来无恙  鲁尼
'Sup, Rooney?
我说过职业巅峰的皮特·鲁尼会把他打球的节奏找回来
Told you prime-time Pete Rooney would find his rhythm.
准备好  我这就要
Ring the alarm bells 'cause I'm on...
火力全开
Fire.
可是我是你女儿
Wait, but I'm your daughter.
你怎么能这么对我
How could you do this to me?
因为迪吉不会在我背后捅刀子
Because Diggy knows not to stab me in the back.
而且他球技不错  起跳有力
Plus, he's a great player with a solid jumper
着装也很有品味
and impeccable fashion sense.
如果你想要让你的对手心神不宁
If you were trying to psych-out your competition,
你们的你的任务达成了
mission accomplished.
别来无恙  迪吉
'Sup, Diggy?
好吧  你先听我说
Okay, before you say anything,
很抱歉我和你爸组队了
I'm sorry that I teamed up with your dad...
也很抱歉我在你面前穿了那条裤子
And that you had to see me in those shorts.
放心  迪吉  我没生你的气
Relax, Diggy. I'm not upset with you.
你没生我的气
You're not?
哇  没想到你这么淡定
Wow, that's really cool of you.
你是很淡定  对吧
You are being really cool, right?
- 姐淡定着呢  - 好的
- Way cool. - Okay.
只不过
It's just...
真不幸
It's too bad though.
天啊  怎么不幸了
Whoa, wait. What's too bad?
哦  你懂的
Oh, you know, it's just
我们不是一队的了  也就是说我们是对手了
we're on different teams now and so we're enemies.
而我觉不会对对手手下留情
And I've sworn to crush all my enemies!
你的意思是说我不能参赛了咯
Are you saying that I can't play
我不会要你做什么的
I would never tell you what to do.
- 好吧  - 嘿
- Okay. - Hey, uh...
你还记得当年我们去溜冰
Do you remember that one time that we went ice skating
我冻得瑟瑟发抖
and I got cold?
当然记得
Of course.
那是我们两个第一次一起出去玩
It was the first time we ever hung out together.
- 你很可爱  - 是啊  这是你当时给我的围巾
- You were so cute. - Yeah, here's the scarf that you loaned me.
好吧
Okay, all right.
我真心感觉你的言下之意
I'm really getting the feeling you're saying
是叫我不要参加这场联赛
not to play in that tournament.
我可什么都没说
I'm not saying anything.
这是你塞进我柜子里面的
Here's a collection of every single note
每一条小纸条
that you've ever left in my locker.
可以了
Okay, okay.
我懂了  我会
I get it. I will, uh...
我会想办法从你爸的队伍里面离开的
I'll find a way to get off your dad's team.
既然如此
I mean...
既然你真心想要这样
If that's what you really want.
教练  我是真心想要参赛
And I really want to play, coach,
只是这手臂有伤
but, ugh, my arm just hurts so bad.
让我直接从巅峰跌落谷底
Cut down in my prime!
超短裤队损失不小啊  是不是  老爸
It's a tough blow to team short-shorts, isn't it, dad?
当然
It sure is.
斯摩尔斯先生  我问你一个问题
Let me ask you one question, Mr. Smalls.
有没有这种可能  玛蒂给你施加了种种压力
Would Maddie, by any chance, be pressuring you...
让你
I don't know... to...
装做这样
Fake this?
马脚漏出来了
Ha ha!
小弟  这女孩对你可不是好消息
That girl's no good for you, son.
啥  爸  你又不喜欢迪吉
What... dad, you don't even like Diggy.
这才不是实话  他人品不错
That's not true. He's a fine young man.
- 真的  伯父  - 迪吉  你别插嘴
- Really, sir? - Stay out of it, Diggy.
- 你别管迪吉的事  - 不可能  我是篮球队教练
- You leave Diggy alone. - No, I'm the basketball coach.
你们两个给我消停一点
You two, knock it off!
- 痛  痛  痛  - 行了  妈
- Ow, ow, ow. - Okay, mom!
我不知道这场争论是谁挑起的
Now, I don't know who started this war,
不过我得踩刹车了  你们两个给我到厨房去
but I'm ending it. Get in the kitchen.
现在就去
Now.
走啊
Now!
漂亮  好啊
Awesome! Yeah!
最后一堂课  我希望你能严加要求
I really want you to dig in on this last session.
我觉得我进步不小
I feel like I've made a lot of progress.
进步马
Progress?
当然
Sure.
这叫进步
Progress.
这就是他所谓的进步
He said progress.
好了
Okey dokey.
开始吧  伯纳德大哥
Let's do this, Bernasty.
伯啥
Bern-who?
伯  你还没到我给你起绰号的地步
Berna... you are not ready for nicknames.
- 只要不是你就行了  - 漂亮的  大个子兄弟
- Not from you. - Good one, tree top.
多谢  帕克小弟
Thanks, p-train.
好吧  约瑟夫  这个练习很简单
All right, Joseph. This is simple.
你只要顶住这些弹力带
All you have to do is run to me
跑到我这里就可以
while fighting those resistance bands.
小事一桩
Oh, piece of cake.
并非所有事都是小事一桩
Everything is not a dessert.
你就像后面墙壁要倒在你身上一样往我这里跑
Run to me as though the walls are chasing you!
我能想象是一群僵尸在追我么
Ooh, can I imagine a zombie?
如果你要这样  也行
If you must.
努力  乔伊  努力  乔伊
Come on, Joey. Dig, Joey!
你只要能碰到我的手掌
All you have to do is touch my hand
你就能成为乔伊 2.5
and you'll be Joey 2.5.
现在我无人能敌了
Whoo! No one can stop me now!
去你的
Buh-bye.
嘿  你愿不愿意在生日派对上表演
Hey, do you do birthday parties?
我的朋友们会很喜欢你的
My pals will really enjoy you.
小事一桩  帕克兄弟
Any time, p-train. Up top.
嗯  两位
Uh, guys.
两位大哥
Dudes?
能不能来帮个忙啊  大个子
A little help over here, tree top?
帕克兄弟
P-train?
救命啊  伯纳德大哥
Help me, bernasty!
你们两个犟头倔脑的家伙
You two are so stubborn.
这个世界上有不少比胜利更重要的事情
Can we at least agree there are more important things than winning?
你们两个从玛蒂五岁起
You two have been playing basketball together
就一起打篮球了
since Maddie was five.
现在你们两个却为了篮球吵得面红耳赤
And now you’re gonna let this wonderful thing you share tear you apart?
- 她先挑起的  - 他先挑起的
- She started it. - He started it.
我觉得你们两个简直就一个模子里刻出来的
I swear, it's like you two are the same person.
是啊  真够意想不到的
I know, shocking.
现在  你们两个把这事给谈开了
Now figure it out.
这世上是不是真的
It is possible
有比胜利更重要的事情
that there are things more important in life than winning?
这话听着别扭  对不对
Doesn't seem right, does it?
很抱歉我把你踢出队了  老爸
I'm sorry I dumped you, dad.
我也很抱歉我把你踢出队了
I'm sorry I dumped you back.
我们现在是不是该拥抱一下了
Are we supposed to hug now or something?
我宁愿去打球
I'd rather go play basketball.
- 那就赶紧去打球吧  - 走吧
- Let's play basketball. - Yeah.
嘿  听着  迪吉
Hey, listen, Diggy.
我还是和玛蒂组队
Um, Maddie and I got back together.
放马来吧
Beat it.
这样的话我也不至于难以启齿了
That actually makes this less awkward.
我和大兄弟组队
I'm teaming up with the big man.
如果你们还有什么疑问
And if anyone's confused,
我就是大兄弟
I'm the big man.
只是提醒你一下  迪吉
Just a warning, Diggy.
大兄弟可是个大错误啊
That big man is a big mistake.
伯纳德戴上眼镜可就牛多了
Bernard is a lot better with his goggles.
哈  怎样
Bam! What?!
我要是能看见篮筐  表现就给力多了
I'm so much better when I can actually see the hoop.
祝你们比赛好运
Good luck in the tournament,
输家
losers.
别
Stop.
亲爱的  我知道在联赛上
Honey, I know it was hard to lose
输给伯纳德和迪吉的滋味不好受
the championship game to Diggy and Bernard,
不过比赛既然结束了
but the tournament's over.
你也改歇一歇了吧
You need to give it up, Pete.
我们明年还有机会能赢回来
But we can win next year.
我指的是你的短裤
No, no. I meant your Daisy Dukes...
你穿着这个  谁都赢不了
'Cause no one wins when you wear those.
嘿  职业巅峰的皮特·鲁尼练习了不少
Hey, prime-time Pete Rooney's been practicing a lot.
球技都回来了
He's got his groove back.
你看看这个
He'd like you to check this out.
盖帽
Oh-ho!
正中靶心  大爷
In your face, old man!
锻炼是很有趣
Exercise is fun.